<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Repro Health</string>
    <string name="Open">Repro Health</string>
    <string name="Close">Repro Health</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="profile">User profile</string>
    <string name="body">Know your body</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="relationships">Relationships</string>
    <string name="family_planning">Family planning</string>
    <string name="diseases">HIV/AIDS and STDs</string>
    <string name="centers">Reproductive health centres</string>
    <string name="stories">Myths and Facts</string>
    <string name="reference">Important references</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="terms">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
       Material is the metaphor.\n\n

       A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion.
       The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet
       technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n
       Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The
       use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the
       flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical
       world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n
       The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move,
       interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows
       seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n

       Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n

       The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color,
       and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the
       eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge
       imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic
       interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n
       An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides
       waypoints for the user.\n\n

       Motion provides meaning.\n\n

       Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are
       inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n
       All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without
       breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n
       Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity.
       Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n

       3D world.\n\n

       The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z
       dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the
       positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single
       position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n
       On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is
       emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n

       Light and shadow.\n\n

       Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create
       directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n
       Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android
       development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at
       various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the
       y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n

       Resting elevation.\n\n

       All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation
       that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting
       elevation as soon as possible.\n\n

       Component elevations.\n\n

       The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation
       does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n
       Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth
       of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n

       Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n

       Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response
       to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation
       changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n
       Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative
       to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent
       across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have
       the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n
       Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting
       elevation.\n\n

       Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n

       Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between
       their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass
       through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways,
       whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n
       On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference.
       For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a
       user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n
       On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference.
       For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere
       when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_user">User Profile</string>
    <string name="title_activity_your_body">Know Youre Body</string>
    <string name="title_activity_relationship">Relationships</string>
    <string name="title_activity_family_planning">Family Planning</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hiv_aids_stds">HIV/AIDS AND STDs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reproductive_centers">Reproductive Centers</string>
    <string name="title_activity_myths_and_facts">Myths And Facts</string>
    <string name="title_activity_references">References</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faqs">FAQ</string>
    <string name="title_activity_terms">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gender_identity">GENDER IDENTITY</string>

    <string name="hello_derrick">Hello derrick!</string>
    <string name="sex_vs_gender">Sex Vs Gender</string>
    <string name="gender_identity">Gender Identity</string>
    <string name="know_youre_body">KNOW YOURE BODY</string>
    <string name="emtions_btn">Understand your emotions</string>
    <string name="sex_btn">Sex and sexuality</string>
    <string name="fertilty_btn">fertility and pregnancy</string>
    <string name="gender_btn">gender Identity</string>
    <string name="sex_vs_gender_btn">Sex Vs gender</string>
    <string name="imageview">image View</string>


    <string name="puberty_btn">What is puberty</string>

    <string name="male_organs_btn">What are male reproductive organs</string>
    <string name="sperms_btn">What are sperms</string>
    <string name="semen_btn">What is semen</string>
    <string name="male_hormones_btn">What are male hormones</string>

    <string name="sex_details">
       <b><u>Sex</u></b>\n
       The term sex refers to biological characteristics, namely chromosomes, internal
       and external sex organs, and the hormonal activities within the body.\n
       Essentially, when we use the term sex, what we are really commenting on is
       “male” vs. “female”, scientifically speaking.\n
       The sex of an individual is based on genetics, making it much more difficult to change.\n
       For those who need a quick recap on human genetics, men and women both possess
       46 chromosomes, as well as two sex chromosomes. Women have two X chromosomes, whereas
       men possess 1 X chromosome and 1 Y chromosome.\n
       It is this Y chromosome in men that causes the testes to form
       (as the Y chromosome is dominant). This difference in chromosomes also causes the
       variation in hormones that are found within the body.\n
       Women, for example, have much higher levels of estrogen and progesterone, which
       stimulate the body to develop primary and secondary sex characteristics
       (breasts, menstruation, etc.).\n
       Men, on the other hand, have much higher levels of testosterone than women. These
       genetically controlled factors result in the physiological and biological
       differences between the sexes.
    </string>

    <string name="gender_details">
       <b><u>Gender</u></b>\n
       Gender describes the characteristics that a society or culture delineates as masculine
       or feminine. It is the role or differentiation that is created by the society.\n\n
       Unlike “sex”, gender does not have a basis in science, although it is affected by the
       biological and physiological characteristics we display as “males” and “females”.\n.
       Instead, gender is based on the societal constructions and belief systems put in place
       that deal with masculinity and femininity. The gender identity that most people adhere to
       is usually unconscious or forced upon us at an early age.\n
       We see the concepts of gender in the colors assigned to children
       (blue for boys, pink for girls), the common length of our hair (men-short, women-long),
       the toys we play with, the jobs we aspire to, and the behaviors and interests we
       are “supposed” to embrace.
    </string>

    <string name="gender_identity_details">
       <b><u>Gender Identity</u></b>\n
       It is more about how do you identify yourself irrespective of your sexual organs.\n
       - If you have male sexual organs and you feel like a male, then your gender is Male\n
       - If you have female sexual organs and you feel like a female, then your gender is Female.\n
       - Sometimes,you may not identify yourself very clearly as one with a male or female gender
       or sometimes you could identify yourself as boy.\n
       Gender identity is different from sexual orientation
    </string>

    <string name="puberty_details">
       <b><u>Puberty</u></b>\n
       Puberty is a stage of transition from childhood to adulthood. All of us grow through this
       difficult stage with changes in our body and mind.\n
       It begins at different ages (from 12 years) depending on different people thus for some it
       starts early and others late. Common changes boys can expect include;\n
       •	Enlargement of testes and the scrotum\n
       •	Growth of pubic hair\n
       •	Enlargement of the penis\n
       •	Ejaculation. During sexual stimulation following a sexual act, the nerves around the
           penis send signals to the surrounding organs and a seminal fluid is released through
           the urethra.\n
       •	Wet dreams. This is common among boys in puberty, they tend to wake up when the beds
           are wet. A boy can have a dream about sex and ejaculates.\n
       •	Change in voice. The voice deepens.
    </string>

    <string name="female_organs_btn">Female reproductive organs</string>

    <string name="female_hormones_details">
       <b><u>FEMALE HORMONES</u></b>\n
       Hormones are the chemical substance that are released into the body by certain glands.The
       brain mainly controls their functione.\n
       They influence the behaviour, moods, and body changes.\n\n
       There are many hormones inour body.Some hormones are specifically responsible for female
       characteristics.
    </string>

    <string name="female_hormone_estrogen_details">
       <b><u>ESTROGEN</u></b>\n
       it is a hormone responsible for female characteristics.\n\n
       In females who are not pregnant, estrogen is mainlt released from the ovaries.\n
       It also controls ovulation. The level of estrogen decreases during menstruation and
       increases during ovulation.\n\n
       In pregnant women, a large a mount of estrogen is also secreted from by the placenta inside
       the uterus.\n\n
       <i>Some effects of estrogen</i>\n
       <b>• Increase in size of sexual organs</b>\n
       During childhood, estrgen is secreted in small amounts, but the level increases in puberty.\n
       This causes all the female sex organs such as the uterus, ovary, fallopian tubes and
       external genitalia such as the vulva and vargina to grow in their sizes\n\n

       <b>• Enlargement of breasts</b>\n
       Before puberty, both male and female breasts are smilar. But it is due to more production
       of estrogen in a female body, the breasts start growing in its size.\n\n

       <b>• Softness of the skin</b>\n
       Estrogen is also responsible for the soft and smooth skin in a female
    </string>

    <string name="female_hormone_progestrone_details">
       <b><u>PROGESTRONE</u></b>\n
       In females who are not pregnant, this hormone is only secreted after the ovulation by a
       structure medically called <i><b>corpus luteum</b></i> in the ovaries\n\n
       In women who are pregnant, large amount of progestrone is secreted by the placenta in the
       uterus\n\n

       <i>Effects of progestrone</i>\n
        <b>• Changes inside uterus</b>\n
        progestrone helps to prepare the uterus for pregnancy after ovulation. It helps in sercretions
        and creating a layer inside the uterus for implantation\n\n

        <b>• Breast development</b>\n
        It is also responsibe for enalarging the breasts.
    </string>

    <string name="female_hormone_fsh_details">
        <b><u>FOLLICLES STIMULATING HORMONE(FSH)</u></b>\n
        It is  the hormone secreted by the pituitary gland in the brain. As the name suggests, it
        stimulates the growth of the varian follicles in the ovary before the release of an egg from
        the follicle during ovulation
    </string>

    <string name="female_hormone_lh_details">
        <b><u>LUTEINIZING HORMONE</u></b>\n
        Pituitary gland in the brain secrets and contols most of the hormone in our body\n\n
        LH is one of the sex hormones produced by pituitary glands. In boys, it mainly controls the
        secretion of testosterone from the testes.\n\n
        If testes produce less testosterone, LH encourages the testes to produce more. If testes
        produce too much testosterone, LH controls testes to produce lesser testosterone.

    </string>

    <string name="ovulation">Ovulation</string>
    <string name="menstruation">Menstruation</string>
    <string name="menstruation_hygiene">Menstruation hygiene</string>
    <string name="menstruation_concerns">Common concerns about menustruation</string>
    <string name="menstruation_myths">Myths about menstruation</string>
    <string name="andolescence_challeges_btn">Challeges of adolescence</string>
    <string name="psychological_btn">Psychological development</string>

    <string name="adolesence_details">
       <b>Adolescence in females</b>\n
       The teenage years are also called adolescence. During this time, the teenager will see
       the greatest amount of growth in height and weight.\n
       Adolescence is a time for growth spurts and puberty changes. An adolescent may grow
       several inches in several months followed by a period of very slow growth,
       then have another growth spurt.\n\n
       Changes with puberty may occur gradually or several signs may become
       visible at the same time.\n
       There is a great amount of variation in the rate of changes that may occur. Some
       adolescents may experience these signs of maturity sooner or later than others.\n
       It is important to remember that these changes happen at different times for
       everyone. Being smaller or bigger than other girls is normal as each child experiences
       puberty at her own time.
    </string>

    <string name="what_is_sex_details">
       <b>What is sex?</b>\n
       Sex is defined as the activities you perform on yourself or with someone else that gives
       you a sexual feeling and pleasure.\n
       Sexual activities range from kissing, touching and the actual act intercourse. It can be
       fan but on the other hand, sex is concerned with huge risks.\n
    </string>

    <string name="sexuality_details">
       <b>What is sexuality?</b>\n
       Sexuality is defined as the capacity of having sexual feelings or desires. Can also mean
       sexual orientation.\n
       Sexuality gives you the idea on sex (good and bad) but having these ideas does not mean
       one is ready for sex.\n
    </string>

    <string name="delaying_sex_details">
       <b>Delaying Sex</b>\n
       Even though having sex is a personal choice, its good to have it at the right time when
       you are mature enough. So for one to have sex, they should be well conversant about the
       risks involved and how to prevent them.\n
       When you are young, mostly during puberty, many of us are uncomfortable with showing our
       bodies and private parts. This does not mean you are abnormal, it just means you are not
       ready to have sex. But do not worry, time will come when you are mature enough.\n
    </string>

    <string name="sex_wrong_reasons_details">
       <b>Wrong reasons to have Sex</b>\n
       You should never have sex for the following reasons:-\n\n
       Because you are lonely, drunk, high.\n
       •Because someone else wants you to.\n
       •Because you think someone owes it to you or you owe it to someone.\n
       •Because of peer pressure i.e wanting to fit in a particular group.\n
       •Because you want to prove to someone that your grown up.\n
       •Because you think having sex will make someone love you or gain popularity and influence.\n
       •When you are afraid to say NO to a person.\n
       •When you think having a baby will make your boyfriend stay in your life.\n
       •When you want someone to return a favor.\n
       •When you want to hurt someone's feelings.
    </string>

    <string name="sexual_intercourse_details">
       <b>What is Sexual Intercourse?</b>\n
       Sexual intercourse is the act of inserting the penis into the vagina that brings out
       pleasure and satisfaction for both women and men.\n
       When intercourse takes place without planning, there are higher risks of unwanted
       pregnancies and can also increase the risk of contracting sexually transmitted infections
       and HIV/AIDS.\n
    </string>

    <string name="masturbation_details">
       <b>Masturbation</b>\n
       Masturbation is the stimulation of the genitals to achieve sexual arousal and pleasure,
       usually to the point of orgasm (sexual climax). It is commonly done by touching, stroking,
       or massaging the penis or clitoris until an orgasm is achieved. Some women also use
       stimulation of the vagina to masturbate or usesex toys,such as a vibrator.\n\n
        <b>Who Masturbates?</b>\n
       Just about everybody. Masturbation is a very common behavior, even among peoplewho have a sex
        partner. In one national study, 95% of males and 89% of females reported that they have
        masturbated.\n\n
       Masturbation is the first sexual act experienced by most males and females. In young children,
        masturbation is a normal part of the growing child's exploration of his or her body.\n\n
       Most people continue to masturbate in adulthood, and many do so throughout their lives.\n
       It becomes unhealthy when you start doing it all the time and can cause back aches but
       does not cause STIs nor pregnancy.
    </string>

    <string name="sexual_orientation_details">
       <b>Sexual Orientation</b>\n
       When one reaches puberty and on wards, sexual attraction grows and increases and it is
        natural and the gender you are attracted to defines the <b><i>sexual orientation</i></b> but
        it does not mean you are ready to have sex.\n\n
       Sexual Orientation is something you realize with in you and can not be forced on you. However,
        sometimes during adoloscence, you can get confused about your own body and also about your
        prefernce and feelings.\n\n
        • If you are attracted to the opposite sex, then you are <b><i>heterosexual</i></b>.\n
        • If you are attracted to the person of the same gender, the you are homosexual i.e
        <b><i>lesbians</i></b> (woman to woman) and <b><i>gay</i></b> (man to man).\n
        • If you are equally attracted to people of the same sex and opposite sex, then you are a
        <b><i>bisexual.</i></b>
    </string>

    <string name="consent_details">
       <b>Consent</b>\n
       Sexual activities are extremely personal. Always respect yourself and your partner as
       well. One must take consent of the other person even for the act of kissing or touching
       their body parts.\n
       If the person says NO then its a NO, you should respect your partner's decision. Hence
       do not force the person physically or emotionally.\n
       Any sexual activity performed without the consent of the other person is considered
       <b>sexual assault</b>
       Sexual assault takes many forms such as forced sexual intercourse, kissing, hugging,
       touching, showing private parts to the other person, masturbating in front of people and
       verbally abusing someone in a sexual tone.\n
    </string>

    <string name="whats_fertility_details">
       <b>What is fertility?</b>\n
       Fertility is the ability to reproduce and bare a child. Men who are fertile are able to
       produce enough healthy sperms to father children. On the other hand, women who are also
       fertile are able to get pregnant and carry the baby inside their uterus and then conceive
       nine months later.\n
       Chances of getting unwanted pregnancies increase when the sexual desires increase
       especially in youths from the age of 15 years to 23 years.
    </string>

    <string name="auses_of_pregnancy_details">
       <b>Causes of pregnancy</b>\n
       Pregnancy can occur during varginal sexual intercourse when the man ejaculates or
       pre-ejaculates into the woman's vagina and  the sperms meet the egg.\n
       Pre-ejaculating involves a small amount of sperms that can be released by the penis before
       complete ejaculation.\n
    </string>

    <string name="avoiding_pregnancy_details">
       <b>How one can avoid pregnancy</b>\n
       The most certain way to a void pregnancy is abstinence (not engaging in
       sexual intercourse at all).Delay sex until you are ready and mature enough to deal with the
       effects of sex.\n
       The other way is the use of modern contraceptives correctly.\n
    </string>

    <string name="when_can_a_female_get_pregnant_details">
       <b><u>When can a female get pregnant?</u></b>\n
       A woman can get pregnant any time of the month or in any phase of her menstrual cycle. One
       can even get pregnant if she has a sexual intercourse during menstruation.\n
       However, the chances of getting pregnant is much higher, few days before and after the
       time of ovulation.\n
       Younger girls (aged 8-9 years) can even get pregnant if they have sexual intercourse even
       before menarche, when the ovulation process has started.
    </string>

    <string name="time_taken_to_be_pregnant_details">
       <b>How long does it take after sex to get pregnant?</b>\n
        Pregnancy does not start at the time when sperm is ejaculated into the vagina.
       It can take up to 3 days for the sperm to meet the egg and fertilize.\n\n
       During these days, sperms travel to the uterus through the fallopian tubes, and then wait
       for the egg to release an ovary.\n
       It then takes another 10 days for the fertilized egg to attach itself to the lining of the
       uterus and this is called <i>implantation</i>. Pregnacy then starts after these processes.\n
       However, sperms travel very fast into the female body and cannot be cleaned or washed thus
       you cannot avoid HIV/STIs or unwanted pregnancy by just washing away the sperms.\n
        </string>

    <string name="fertilization_details">
       <b>What is fertilization?</b>\n
       The joining of the egg and sperms is called fertilization. It occurs after a sexual
       intercourse when sperms are ejaculted into the vagina and meet the egg. Usually, out of
       a million sperms released, only one sperm meets the egg and gets fertilized.\n
    </string>

    <string name="implantation_details">
       <b>What is Implantation?</b>\n
       The fertilized egg moves down the follopian tube and divides into more cells, forming a
       ball. The ball of the cells reaches the uterus about 3-4 days after fertilization. The
       ball floats in the uterus for another 2-3 days.\n\n
       Pregnancy begins only if the ball cells attach to the ligning of the uterus and this is
       called <i>Implantation</i>.\n
       It usually starts about six days after fertilization and takes about 3-4 days to
       be complete. Up to half of all fertilized eggs never implant, they pass out of women's
       bodies during menstruation.\n
       If implantation takes place successfully, the attached ball of cells further divides to
       form the shapes and size of the baby along with the formation of the placenta.\n
    </string>

    <string name="determine_pregnancy_details">
        <b>How can one know if she is pregnant</b>\n
         Missing the period would be the first sign of pregnancy.\n
        If ou have had sex, wether it is was protected with use of contraceptives or it was
        unprotected, if your period is late, always take a regnancy test. You will have to consul a
        doctor for further information if the pregnancy test turnes out to be positive\n\n
        If you get pregnant at a young age like in teenage, it is often risky for your health.\n\n

        In such circumstances, you will have to inform your parents, or any elders you trust and
        must visit a doctor to discuss about further plans.\n
        There are many help centers tht can help adolescents and youth like you and they wont judge
        you and your information will remain confidential with them\n\n
        If you find out that you are pregnant and it was not planned, never ever do someting on your
        own or put something inside your vagina or harm yourself or your body. Always consult  doctor
        as soon as you find out that you are pregnant
    </string>

    <string name="pregnancy_myths_details">
       If a male does not ejaculate dring sexual intercourse,girl can\'t get pregnant.\n
       No, a woman can get pregnant because of the pre-ejaculated semen can contain sperms, so
       there are chances of getting pregnant even when sperms are not ejaculated into the vagina.
    </string>

    <string name="female_puberty_details">
       <b>What is puberty in females?</b>\n
       Puberty is a stage of transition from childhood to adulthood. All of us grow through this
        difficult stage with changes in our body and mind.\n
       It begins at different ages (from 9 years) depending on different people thus for some
        it starts early and others late. Common changes girls can expect include;\n
       •	Enlargement of breasts.\n
       •	Growth of pubic hair.\n
       •	Change in body shape. Girls have lesser muscle mass and more fat mass than boys do,
        so during puberty many girls tend to gain weight, gain hips. It is a normal process though,
        so girls shouldn’t worry.\n
       •	Menstruation. The first period in a girl’s life is called menarche, it may begin as
        early as 8 years to as late as 16 years. It is the time when a girl starts bleeding
        from the vagina for 4-5 days every month.
    </string>

    <string name="female_organs_details">
        <b><u>FEMALE REPRODUCTIVE ORGANS</u></b>\n
        Reproductive organs are those organs in our bpdy that help in the process of reproduction.\n
        As these organs are also involved in sexual functions, they are also called
        <i><b>sexual organs</b></i>\n
        In girls, some reproductive organs are inside and some outside the body.
    </string>

    <string name="female_organs_vulval_details">
        <b><u>Vulva</u></b>\n
        The vulval is made up of other reproductive parts among which include the following:-\n\n
        <b>Labia</b>\n
        Labia stands for lip in Latin language because it looks like lips. Labia covers rest of the
        vulva. The outer part of labia is medically called labia majora. It can be of different
        sizes and are usually darker in color. It contains the public hair on it.\n\n
        When a woman gets sexually excited, the outer lip(labia majora)swells up and color
        lightens.\n\n
        Inside the outer lip, there is another set of inner lip which is more sensitive and more
        pinkish in color. This inner lip is medically called <b><i>labia minora</i></b>\n\n

        <b>Clitoris</b>\n
        The clitoris is located in the upper part of vulva. The inner lips of labia come together
        to form a hood or roof to cover the clitoris.\n\n
        It is the most sensitive sexual organ in a woman's body which is rich in nerve supply.\n\n
        It can vary in size from a size of pea to the size of finger-tip. It is comparable to the
        penis in male but with less function.\n\n
        The only function of clitoris is to provide sexual pleasure to female.\n\n
        When a female gets sexually excited, the clitoris gets firmer and bigger.\n\n

        <b>Urethre</b>\n
        Many young girls get confused about where the urine actually comes out of.\n\n
        Many think it is the clitoris that passes the urine out.\n\n
        But actually the urine comes out from the urethre, which is a small hole that lies just
        below the clitoris.\n\n

        <b>Vaginal opening</b>\n
        It is the opening that connects the outer sexual organs to the inner sexual organs.\n\n
        It lies at the point where the inner lips of the labia meet.\n\n
        It leads to the passage called vagina.
    </string>

    <string name="female_organs_hymen_details">
        <b><u>HYMEN</u></b>\n
        It is a membrane that partly covers the vaginal opening from inside. In young girls, it
        could be intact. In later years in most sexually active women it may be absent or a small
        remnant may remain.\n\n
        However, even in young girls and virgins the hymen may have already been torn because of
        physical exercises such as cycling etc.\n\n
        Tearing of hymen is normal and it does not have any harmful effect on health.\n\n
        In many traditions people believe intact hymen is a sign of virginity is NOT true!
    </string>

    <string name="female_organs_cervix_details">
        <b><u>CERVIX</u></b>\n
        In Latin, cervix stands for neck. So it is the narrow and the lower part of the uterus. It
        is the openeing of the uterus that connects t the vagina.\n
        This part is highly prone to cancer. In Nepal cancer of cervix is one of the most common
        cancer among women
    </string>
    <string name="female_organs_breast_details">
        <b><u>BREAST</u></b>\n
        A female breast is part of the reproductive system because it produces milk when a woman
        gives birth.\n\n
        It is a sensitive organ and touching it could also give sexual pleasure. As it is sensitive
        it can get hurt easily as well.\n\n
        The size of the breasts do not affect the milk producing capacity. It des not affect the
        sexual pleasure or sexul activity either.\n\n
        It is important for girls and women to take care of their breasts and do regular
        self-breast examination. Breast is a common site of cancer for most women.
    </string>


    <string name="menstruation_details">
       <b>What is Menstruation?</b>\n
       It is the monthly bleeding that takes place at the end of a menstruation cycle.\n
       Following ovulation, if the egg doesn’t meet the sperm, it is not fertilized. In this case
        hormones drop and the inner lining of the uterus that was preparing itself for
        pregnancy begins to shed which causes bleeding.\n
       The blood travels through the cervix to the vagina and comes out of the vagina opening.\n
       The bleeding days and amount of bleeding vary from person to person.
    </string>

    <string name="menstruation_hygiene_details">
       <b>MENSTRUATION HYGIENE</b>\n
       It is very important for girls to have a good hygiene during menstruation i.e. keep the
        genitalia clean and dry during menstruation to prevent creation of room for bacteria and
        other microorganisms to grow which can lead to an infection.\n
       There are different menstrual hygiene products a girl can use and the include;\n
       •	Sanitary pads.\n
       •	Tampons.\n
       •	Menstrual cups.\n
       •	Reusable cotton clothes.\n
    </string>

    <string name="menstruation_concerns_details">
       <b>Common menstrual concerns.</b>\n
       Most girls face emotional and physical problems during menstruation.
        And below is some detail of how to deal with it;\n\n

       <b>Premenstrual symptoms.</b> 40% of women/girls experience it and does not have any
        specific characteristics though different people encounter different issues.\n
       Common ones are; irritability, mood swings and angry outbursts, feeling fullness in the
       body. One can cope up with these issues by; eating healthy food, physical activities such
       as exercise and sports and reducing the stress through having yoga classes.\n\n

       <b>Pain during menstruation.</b> Most girls experience pain during menstruation because the
       uterus contracts to push out blood from it. This can be moderated by;\n
       •	Having exercises such as walking to improve blood flow.\n
       •	Having a healthy diet.\n
       •	Applying heat to your abdomen with a heating pad or a hot water bottle can
       relieve the pain.\n
       •	Taking a warm shower and having a massage can help relieve discomfort.\n\n

       <b>Irregular cycles.</b> A normal cycle may vary from 28-35 days depending on an
       individual.\n
       In a young girl, there are lots of hormonal changes and the process of ovulation may not
       have been normal yet. Thus, it is common for young girls to have irregular cycles until
       the age of 21 years.\n
       Sometimes factors like stress, and lack of nutrition can lead to irregular cycles. Hence it
       is important to eat healthy and have regular exercises but if the irregularity persist,
       seek medical attention from a doctor.\n
    </string>

    <string name="menstruation_myths1_details">
       <b>A girl or woman is impure and dirty during menstruation, hence should not enter
        the kitchen or temples</b>\n
       No! Menstruation is a natural process that indicates a healthy reproductive cycle and is
        not a judge of purity of cleanlness of a woman.
       However a woman is supposed to maintain hygiene during this period just like any other
        days.\n
       There is nothing wrong with entering the kitchen or having or having your faith in God
        during this period.
    </string>

    <string name="menstruation_myths2_details">
       <b>A girl or woman having periods should just take a bath on the fourth day of
            menstruation to purify her.</b>\n
       No! A girl should take a bath everyday to maintain hygiene during menstruation or any
        other days.
    </string>

    <string name="menstruation_myths3_details">
       <b>A girl should never discuss about her periods with other males</b>\n
       No, even men can provide help during menstruation such as counselling, be supportive. So
       both males and females are involved.
    </string>

    <string name="menstruation_myths4_details">
       <b> A girl or a woman should never touch a man during menstruation</b>


    </string>

    <string name="menstruation_myths5_details">
       <b>A girl or a woman should not exercise during menstruation</b>\n
       No, actually exercises and yoga help improve blood flow and do not harm your body.\n
    </string>

    <string name="menstruation_myths6_details">
       <b>A girl or a woman should not swim during menstruation</b>\n
       No, one can do any activity she wants during menstruation just like in any other days.
       It is just that some sanitary napkins are not water proof, hence there will be some
       leaking.\n
    </string>

    <string name="menstruation_myths7_details">
       <b>Virgins should not use tampons</b>\n
       No, tamptons serve the same purpose as sanitary napkins and do not have any negative
       effect on one's virginity. However, it is important to know how to use them correctly.\n
    </string>

    <string name="menstruation_myths9_details">
       <b>One must not have sex during menstruation because the menstruation blood releases toxins
           into the male body</b>\n
       No, there is no problem having sex during this period as long as both parties agree on the
       issue since it is not hygienic.\n
       However, having sex during this period increases the chance of getting HIV and STIs as well
       as pregnancy.\n
    </string>

    <string name="ovulation_details">
       <b><u>What is Ovulation</u></b>\n
       This is a time when an egg is released from the ovarian follicles in the ovaries with
       the help of different female hormones.\n
       The egg is released in the ovary and then travels to the fallopian tube and fertilization
       takes place if a sperm meets an ovum.\n
    </string>

    <string name="male_organs_details">
       <b><u>What are Male Organs?</u></b>\n
        Unlike the female reproductive system, most of the male reproductive system is located
       outside of the body. These external structures include the penis, scrotum, and
       testicles.\n\n

       <b><u>Penis:</u></b>\n
       This is the male organ used in sexual intercourse. It has three parts: the root, which
       attaches to the wall of the abdomen; the body, or shaft; and the glans, which is the
       cone-shaped part at the end of the penis.\n
       The glans, also called the head of the penis, is covered with a loose layer of skin
       called foreskin. This skin is sometimes removed in a procedure called circumcision.\n
       The opening of the urethra, the tube that transports semen and urine, is at the tip
       of the penis. The glans of the penis also contains a number of sensitive nerve endings.\n
       The body of the penis is cylindrical in shape and consists of three circular shaped
       chambers. These chambers are made up of special, sponge-like tissue.
       This tissue contains thousands of large spaces that fill with blood when the man is
       sexually aroused.\n
       As the penis fills with blood, it becomes rigid and erect, which allows for penetration
       during sexual intercourse. The skin of the penis is loose and elastic to accommodate
       changes in penis size during an erection.\n\n

       <b><u>Scrotum:</u></b>\n
       This is the loose pouch-like sac of skin that hangs behind and below the penis.\n
       It contains the testicles (also called testes), as well as many nerves and blood vessels.\n
       The scrotum acts as aclimate control system for the testes. For normal sperm development,
        the testes must be at a temperature slightly cooler than body temperature.\n
       Special muscles in the wall of the scrotum allow it to contract and relax, moving the
       testicles closer to the body for warmth or farther away from the body to cool temperatures.\n\n
       <b><u>Testicles (testes):</u></b>\n
       These are oval organs about the size of large olives that lie in the scrotum, secured
       at either end by a structure called the spermatic cord. Most men have two testes.\n
       The testes are responsible for making testosterone, the primary male sex hormone, and for
       generating sperm. Within the testes are coiled masses of tubes called seminiferous
       tubules. These tubes are responsible for producing sperm cells.
    </string>

    <string name="semens_details">
       <b><u>What is Semen?</u></b>\n
       Semen is a fluid that is ejaculated from the penis. It is white in color and mucus like
       in nature.\n
       It consists of fluid collected from the vas deferens, fluid from prostate and seminal
       vesicles.\n
       Semen contains sperm (reproductive cells), is expelled (ejaculated) through the end of
       the penis when the man reaches sexual climax (orgasm). When the penis is erect, the flow
       of urine is blocked from the urethra, allowing only semen to be ejaculated at orgasm.
    </string>

    <string name="sperm_details">
       <b><u>What are Sperms?</u></b>\n
       Sperm is the male reproductive cell. Boys start producing sperms from puberty.\n
       The testes produce up to 120 sperms per day and most of them are stored in the
        vas deferens.\n
       They can remain stored maintaining their fertility up to one month.\n
       During the storage, the sperms are in an inactive state and become active during
       ejaculation(after a sexual activity) and are capable of fertilization.
       when it meets the ovum. Only one sperm is needed for fertilization.
    </string>

    <string name="male_hormones_details">
       <b><u>What are male hormones?</u></b>\n
       Hormones are the chemical substances that are released into the body by certain glands
       and are mainly controlled by the brain.\n
       They influence the behavior, moods and body changes. Some hormones are specifically
       responsible for male characteristics and sperm formation and these include;\n\n

       <b><u>Testosterone</u></b>\n
       Testerone is the hormone responsible for sperm formation. When a male baby is inside the
       mother's womb, testosterone is produced until puberty.\n
       These hormones are mainly produced by the testes in men. The secretion of testesterone is
       controlled by the hormones screted by piuitary gland located in the brain.\n
       This hormone is responsible for;\n
        •Enlargement of sexual organs.\n
        •Distribution of body hair.\n
        •Changes in the voice.\n
        •Muscle development.\n
        •Bone growth.\n\n

       <b><u>Luteinizing Hormone(LH)</u></b>\n
       Pituitary gland in the brain secretes and controls most of the hormones in our body.
       LH is one of the sex hormones produced by pituitary glands. In boys, it mainly controls the
       secretion of testosterone from the testes.\n
       If testes produce less testosterone, LH encourages the testes to produce more.\n\n

       <b><u>Estrogens</u></b>\n
       Boys secrete estrogens but in lesser amount and help in sperm formation.\n
       <b>Follicle Stimulting Hormone (FSH)</b>\n
       Produced by the pituitary gland and facilitates sperm formation.\n\n

       <b><u>Growth Hormones</u></b>\n
       These are mainly responsible for overall growth but also help in sperm formation.
    </string>

    <string name="signs_btn">Signs of healthy and unhealthy relationships</string>

    <string name="special_btn">Relationship with someone special</string>

    <string name="friend_btn">Relationship with friends</string>

    <string name="parents_btn">Relationship with parents and elders</string>

    <string name="key_btn">Key to healthy relationship</string>

    <string name="details_btn">Relationship</string>

    <string name="relationship_details">
       <b><u>Relationship</u></b>\n
       Adolescence and youth is the phase of life when you start exploring more about your
       relationships.
        </string>

    <string name="relationship_friend_details">
       <b><u>Relationship</u></b>\n
       A key to successful friendship is being with the right company. So learn to choose the
       right friends as a youth because they have a bigger influence in your life.\n\n
       <b><u>A real Friend</u></b>\n
        • Someone you are natural and free with.\n
        • Someone yo do not work hard to impress.\n
        • A person with whom you share common interests and understands you.\n\n
       <b>Do not have company with people that:-</b>
        •bully you and disrespect you.\n
        •Force you into doing risky and unhealthy activities such as smoking, alcohol, risky
       sexual activities.\n

    </string>

    <string name="relationship_key_details">
       <b><u>Key to healthy relationships</u></b>\n
       The first step towards a healthy relationship begins from you.\n\n

       <b>Communicate.</b>\n
       Communication is a fundamental aspect in a successful relationship and it
       helps both parties to understand each other very well. It is a two way thing where by both
       parties have to be involved so as to create a smooth relationship.\n\n
       <b>Learn to listen.</b>\n
       You should be able to listen to your partner no matter the circumstances and this creates
        trust.\n\n

       <b>Be honest.</b>\n
       Always be faithful and truthful to your partner.\n
       Have a positive attitude.\n
       Always appreciate your partner and be supportive where necessary.\n
    </string>

    <string name="relationship_parents_details">
       <b><u>Relationship With Parents and Elders</u></b>\n
       A relationship with your parents and elders may seem more complicated during this phase. In
       most cases, you think you are old and big enough to make your own decisions which may be
       rational.\n
       You tend to think everything they tell you is not important but in real sense, they are
       trying to protect you because you are precious to them and they love you.\n
    </string>

    <string name="relationship_signs_details">
       <b>Signs of Healthy and Unhealthy Relationships</b>\n
       A healthy relationship with someone special be it your girlfriend or boyfriend must
       be mutual where:\n
       • Both respect each other.\n
       • Both parties respect and are honest with one another.\n
       • Both clearly communicate no matter the circumstances and express themselves.\n
       • Both have mutual consent for sexual activities and ready to go for an HIV test.\n
    </string>

    <string name="relationship_special_details">
       <b><u>Relationship with someone special</u></b>\n
       As we grow older, it is natural for us to wish we could be special for that one person. We
       also develop sexual feelings, feelings of intimacy and bonding with someone special. A
       healthy relationship is always comfortable and less complicated.\n
       Thus it is advised t have healthy relationships where;\n
        •You can be free and natural with someone.\n
        •You love and respect someone unconditionally.\n
    </string>

    <string name="temporary_btn">Temporary Methods</string>

    <string name="permanent_btn">Permanent Methods</string>

    <string name="emergency_btn">Emergency Contraceptives</string>

    <string name="others">Others</string>

    <string name="intrauterine_contraceptives">
       <b><u>Intrauterine contraceptive device(IUCD) or Intrauterine device(IUD).</u></b>\n
       It is a flexible, small T-shaped tube that is inserted inside the uterus.\n
       It is effective for 12 years and is used by women who do not want to give birth for
       a long period. There are various types of IUDs and the most common one is copper-T.\n
       However, it requires a trained health worker, and can be accessed from
       a health facility.\n
    </string>

    <string name="implants">
       <b><u>Hormonal contraceptive implants.</u></b>\n
       These are small tubes that contain a form of progesterone hormone in them. A trained
       health worker inserts the tubes under the skin of the woman’s upper arm. It
       is effective for 5 years.\n
       It releases the progesterone slowly into the woman’s body for a period of 5 years
       and prevents ovulation and thickens mucus in the cervix which prevents fertilization.\n
    </string>

    <string name="injection_contraceptives">
       <b><u>Contraceptive Injection.</u></b>\n
       This is used by women who do not want to give birth for a long time. Just a single dose
       of contraceptive injection can prevent pregnancy for 3 months.\n
       The contraceptive injection is commonly known as DEPO based on the type of progesterone
       hormone it contains. It prevents ovulation and thickens mucus in the cervix which
       prevents fertilization.\n
       However, it must be used after consulting the doctor and requires trained staff.
    </string>

    <string name="oral_contraceptives">
       <b><u>Oral Contraceptive pills.</u></b>\n
       These are pills that are taken by females through the
       mouth. It doesn’t prevent HIV or STIs! There are two types of oral contraceptive pills;\n
       Combined oral contraceptive pills. Most commonly used type. Contains two hormones called
       estrogen and progesterone. It prevents ovulation and thickens mucus in the cervix
       which prevents fertilization.\n
       Minipill or Progesterone pill. This contains only one hormone called the progesterone and
       is suitable for mothers who are breast feeding.\n
    </string>

    <string name="condom">
       <b><u>Condom</u>.</b>\n
       This is a commonly used method of contraception, acts as a barrier between
       the genitalia, prevents exchange of body fluids and entry of sperm into the
       vagina during sexual intercourse.\n
       It can prevent pregnancy, HIV and other STIs when used consistently and correctly for
       each and every sexual intercourse.\n
    </string>

    <string name="temporary_contraceptives">
       <b><u>Temporary modern contraceptives.</u></b>\n
       Temporary modern contraceptives. These are devices that can prevent pregnancy temporarily.
       It could be effective for one episode of sexual intercourse, a month, 3 months, 5 years
       or even 12 years depending on the type of contraceptive used.\n
       These methods are effective only if used correctly and are reversible in case
       one wants to get pregnant. These include;\n
    </string>

    <string name="tubal_ligtion_details">
       <b><u>Tubal Ligagtion</u></b>\n
       This is a surgical procedure done in women, where the fallopian tubes are either tied or
       cut, so the ovum does not meet the sperm for fertilization.\n
    </string>

    <string name="vasectomy_details">
       <b>Vasectomy.</b>\n
       This is a major surgery done in men where the vas deferens are tied
       or cut. A man who had vasectomy will still have ejaculation but the ejaculated semen
       will not mix with the sperms thus prevent fertilization.\n
       However, after vasectomy, it is advised for men to have protected sex for a period of
       6 months because the man will still ejaculate sperm in that period which may cause
       unwanted pregnancies.\n
    </string>

    <string name="permanent_details">
       <b><u>Permanent Methods.</u></b>\n
       These are methods that forever prevent pregnancy and is a choice of couples who never
       want to have children ever again.
    </string>

    <string name="emergency_details">
        <b><u>Emergence contraceptives.</u></b>\n
       Sometimes, one could forget to use other contraceptives before having sex and other cases,
       the condom may slip off or tear. In these cases, unprotected sex could increase the risk
       of unwanted pregnancy.\n
       There are methods that can be used within a certain duration after unprotected sexual
       intercourse that can prevent pregnancy. However, these methods do not prevent
       HIV/STIs. These include;\n
       •	Contraceptive pills\n
       •	IUDs
    </string>

    <string name="IUD_details">
       <b><u>IUD</u></b>\n
       It is effective for 12 years and is used by women who do not want to give birth for
       a long period. There are various types of IUDs and the most common one is copper-T.\n
       However, it requires a trained health worker, and can be accessed from
       a health facility.\n
    </string>

    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section:</string>

    <string name="psyco_details">
        <b><u>PSYCHOLOGICAL DEVELOPMENT</u></b>\n
        Just like your body, there are lots of changes in your emotions  nd psychology during
        adolescence and youth\n\n

        Some issues and challenges you notice at this phase of your life include the following:-
    </string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="female_hormones_btn">Female hormones</string>

    <string name="psyco_identity_details">
        <b><u>IDENTITY</u></b>\n
        This is the time you start exploring your identity. About who you are 
        and what you want to become in life.\n\n
        You start developing your own beliefs based on what your parents, your
        friends and the society around think and do.\n\n

        Sometimes, you are inspired and influenced by your surrounding and 
        sometimes you feel you do not fit in.\n\n

        Sometimes, you may also begin to feel strongly about a religion and 
        about your ethnicity. Sometimes you may not.\n\n

        Don\'t worry, you can be very confused right now. You do not have to
        rush to take any serious decisions about your beliefs. Beliefs keep
        changing even when you become an adult.\n\n
        You will have clearer idea in few years about how you would like to
        identify yourself in different areas of your life.
    </string>

    <string name="psyco_sadness_and_depression_details">
        <b><u>SADNESS AND DEPRESSION</u></b>\n
        It is natural to feel sad many times.You might feel like you don\'t
        fit in and nobody understands you.\n\n
        Sometimes, you might also feel depressed. If you find it is too 
        difficult for you, you should always talk to someone.\n\n
        It is better to talk to your parents and teachers or other elders
        you feel comfortable with. It is always better to focus your energy
        in physical activities like sports, art and music, that would make
        you feel better. But even after you try your best, if you still 
        feel\n\n
        -too sad\n\n
        -too many thoughts always bothering you\n\n
        -always feel like crying constantly\n\n
        -cannot sleep\n\n
        -don\'t feel like eating or eat too much\n
        You needto ask for help from your parents, elders and even 
        professionals who can help you deal with difficult times.
    </string>

    <string name="psyco_sucidal_thoughts_details">
        <b><u>SUCIDAL THOUGHTS</u></b>\n
        Everyone of us at any age, at any point of life can feel very sad and 
        depressed to the extent you start hating your life.\n
        Life is difficult for all, but there are also millions of opportunities and
        hopes.\n
        What bothers you right now will stop bothering you when you are emotionally
        strong and grow up a bit more. In few years you might even feel like laughing 
        at yourself.\n
        If you have constant feeling of harming yourself or even kill yourself:\n\n
        -Do not rush\n\n
        -Take a deep breath and ask for help immediately from your elders\n\n
        -Do not hurt yourself\n\n
        You are too precious to be harmed by yourself or by anyone else\n\n
        Always remember you are special no matter whatt happened to you or what
        other people think of you.\n\n
        There are many professional health centers who can help you feel better.
        They will not judge you. They understand what you are going through.
        There are many adolescents like you who feel sad and anxious everyday.
        You are not the only one. Talk to your parent or elders.
    </string>

    <string name="psyco_substance_abuse_details">
        <b><u>SUBSTANCE ABUSE</u></b>\n
        Adolescence is a time when you are at high risk of indulging in smoking,
        drinking alcohol and taking drugs.\n\n
        But once you take these steps, it is difficult for you to give up these
        habits. Even worse, you can easily get addicted. It can get you into wrong
        company and you may have trouble with the people you love.\n\n
        But you have a bright future ahead of you and you should not ruin it.\n\n
        So control yourself. Learn to say NO to substance abuse. Instead focus your 
        energy on education,games and sports, art and music or whatever makes you
        feel really good inside.\n\n
        You can be happy and have fun even without these substances.\n\n
        In fact, you will be much happier without them.
    </string>

    <string name="psyco_eating_problems_details">
        <b><u>EATING PROBLEMS</u></b>\n
        It is common for many adolescents both boys and girls to have eating 
        problems.\n\n
        As your body and mind is growing, it is important for you to have proper
        nutrition.\n\n
        If you are conscious of your body image and eat too little, it can lead
        to malnutrition and imbalance in your hormones affecting your normal
        growth.\n\n
        If you think you are not growing enough and eat too much, it will not 
        help either, because it can lead to problems like obesity and can also 
        affect your hormones and your proper growth.\n\n
        So try to have a balance diet rich in all the nutrients.\n\n
        Too much or too little food is not healthy for your growth.\n\n
        You should consult a professional nutritionist if you are having
        eating problems.
    </string>

    <string name="psyco_anger_and_aggression_details">
        <b><u>ANGER AND AGGRESSION</u></b>\n
        At your age it is normal to get angry more often with your parents 
        and elders.\n\n
        Anger is a natural emotion that we all have.\n\n
        But it is more important to learn to control your anger.\n\n
        It is not cool to let your anger control you.\n\n
        It is not cool to destroy things around you and hurt people.\n\n
        When you feel angry you can instead divert your anger and 
        frustration into something productive like running, playing sports,
        playing music or painting or writing.\n\n
        This way you can channel all your negative energy into something
        more creative that you can be proud of.\n\n
        Many of us often laugh at the things that used to make us angry
        when we were younger. So don't worry it is a matter of time. Do
        not let aggression take over all the good things you have within 
        you.
    </string>

    <string name="psyco_self_esteem_details">
        <b><u>ANGER AND SELF ESTEEM</u></b>\n
        Once you enter puberty and the days onwards, you notice sudden changes
        in your body and emotions. We all become selfconscious.We are concerned
        about what others think of us.\n\n
        In this process some may become extremely shy, some may loose their
        confidence, whereas some may try to gain too much attention from 
        others.\n\n
        But the best solution is to stay cool.You do not need to worry
        about what your friends think of you because they are going through the
        similar stage as awkward as it is for you.\n\n
        You also do not need to worry what your elders think of you, bacause they
        too have passed through your stage.At your age they too have gone through
        their own awkwardness.\n\n
        So take it easy,relax and understand that you are still growing.Have 
        confidence in yourself because no matter what others think of you,
        you are special.You will turn out just fine as a wonderful adult.
     
    </string>

    <string name="psyco_body_image_details">
        <b><u>BODY IMAGE</u></b>\n
        As we enter puberty our body changes rapidly.We all want to  look attractive
        and are often influenced by the images of models and actors you watch in 
        movies and magazines etc.On the other hand, you may feel that you do not
        look like them.\n\n
        Relax, we all have been through this stage.It is normal.Even the attractive
        adults you admire could have gone through same problems when they were
        younger.\n\n
        Remember, it is not the shape of your body,how fat you are or how thin
        you are that makes you attractive.Instead, it is the personality and the 
        confidence you have in yourself that will make you attractive.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>


    //fire base

    <string name="label_google_sign_in">Firebase + Google Sign In</string>
    <string name="desc_google_sign_in">Use a Google Sign In credential to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_facebook_login">Firebase + Facebook Login</string>
    <string name="desc_facebook_login">Use a Facebook Login credential to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_twitter_login">Firebase + Twitter Login</string>
    <string name="desc_twitter_login">Use a Twitter Login credential to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_emailpassword">Email/Password Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_emailpassword">Use an email and password to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_passwordless">Passwordless Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_passwordless">Use only an email to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_phone_auth">Phone Number Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_phone_auth">Use a phone number to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_anonymous_auth">Anonymous Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_anonymous_auth">Sign in anonymously and then later upgrade to a full Firebase Auth user.</string>

    <string name="label_custom_auth">Custom Authentication</string>
    <string name="desc_custom_auth">Use a custom token signed by your own server to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="label_firebase_ui">FirebaseUI Auth</string>
    <string name="desc_firebase_ui">Use the FirebaseUI-Android library to authenticate with Firebase.</string>

    <string name="hint_user_id">User ID</string>
    <string name="get_custom_token">Get Token</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="create_account">Create Account</string>
    <string name="send_link">Send Link</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="verify_email">Verify Email</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="custom_token">Custom Token</string>
    <string name="signed_in">Signed In</string>
    <string name="signed_out">Signed Out</string>
    <string name="token_null">Token: null</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="desc_firebase_lockup">Firebase logo and name</string>
    <string name="auth_failed">Authentication failed</string>
    <string name="start_phone_auth">Start</string>
    <string name="verify_phone_auth">Verify</string>
    <string name="resend_phone_auth">Resend</string>
    <string name="hint_phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="hint_verification_code">Verification Code</string>
    <string name="status_code_sent">Code Sent</string>
    <string name="status_verification_failed">Verification failed</string>
    <string name="status_verification_succeeded">Verification succeeded</string>
    <string name="status_sign_in_failed">Sign-in failed</string>
    <string name="instant_validation">(instant validation)</string>

    <string name="firebase_status_fmt">Firebase User: %s</string>
    <string name="firebase_user_management">Firebase User Management</string>

    <string name="google_status_fmt">Google User: %s</string>
    <string name="google_title_text">Google Sign In</string>

    <string name="facebook_status_fmt">Facebook User: %s</string>
    <string name="facebook_title_text">Facebook Login</string>

    <string name="emailpassword_status_fmt">Email User: %1$s (verified: %2$b)</string>
    <string name="emailpassword_title_text">Email and Password</string>

    <string name="passwordless_status_fmt">Email User: %1$s (verified: %2$b)</string>
    <string name="passwordless_title_text">Passwordless Sign In</string>
    <string name="status_email_not_sent">Send link to your email to get started.</string>
    <string name="status_email_sent">Link sent, check your email to continue.</string>
    <string name="status_link_found">Link received, enter email to sign in.</string>

    <string name="phone_title_text">Phone Number</string>

    <string name="twitter_status_fmt">Twitter User: %s</string>
    <string name="twitter_title_text">Twitter Login</string>

    <string name="firebaseui_status_fmt">Firebase User: %s</string>
    <string name="firebaseui_title_text">FirebaseUI Auth</string>

    <string name="id_fmt">User ID: %s</string>
    <string name="email_fmt">Email: %s</string>


    //firebase styles

    <!-- Dark Buttons -->
    <style name="ThemeOverlay.MyDarkButton" parent="ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Dark">
        <item name="colorButtonNormal">@color/grey_500</item>
        <item name="colorAccent">@color/colorAccent</item>
        <item name="android:layout_marginRight">4dp</item>
        <item name="android:layout_marginLeft">4dp</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">@android:color/white</item>
    </style>

    <!-- Light EditTexts -->
    <style name="ThemeOverlay.MyLightEditText" parent="ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Dark" />

    <style name="ThemeOverlay.MyTextDetail" parent="AppTheme">
        <item name="android:layout_width">wrap_content</item>
        <item name="android:layout_height">wrap_content</item>
        <item name="android:fadeScrollbars">true</item>
        <item name="android:gravity">center</item>
        <item name="android:maxLines">5</item>
        <item name="android:padding">4dp</item>
        <item name="android:scrollbars">vertical</item>
        <item name="android:textSize">14sp</item>
    </style>

    <style name="ThemeOverlay.FirebaseIcon" parent="AppTheme">
        <item name="android:layout_marginTop">@dimen/icon_top_margin</item>
        <item name="android:layout_marginBottom">@dimen/icon_bottom_margin</item>
    </style>

    <style name="ThemeOverlay.MyTitleText" parent="AppTheme">
        <item name="android:gravity">center</item>
        <item name="android:textSize">36sp</item>
    </style>

    <string name="title_activity_login2">Sign in</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>


</resources>
